I i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i. Joined.
One of our old.
And I. Were born.
Not recording I try. To forward.
Where.
Is your bottle green and I hope I
will never hold witnesses
in the oil with good small
hurt when I put the. Two
First enough I am forced to
take
a man. In this new code of that is in
. The following week understand to be
a little in the load with mildly you when.
You were in my dream comes true for.
LOYOLA to get you. But I was not
the. World's Burger
King live in New Orleans
but advantage. In the.
Old Girl where in Europe
all your are. Lul my good.
Old boy.
Just give me five minutes and I'll have
the other number ready I get a small X.
Number of boys.
The battle the body of public and. Smear
Yeah but ten against one that's not very
sad Come on. What's it all
about. You had to tell me
no I'm not
a scared by Huey. And if I can help it I
just want to know why the gang was like
you we don't want a man I'm
a burglar going to high school I do here
why don't you what's he got smallpox is
something was wrong like. His
religion that Mr he did all the time
I see what you mean you must be
a bunch of those nazi Willetts I've been
reading about. Maybe I'm an American Well
I think we are not see don't call me
a Nazi my father talked to me on the committee
but we didn't say it but he got some
of that blood plasma not so bad I had
a good three times son anybody no family
ever go to the blood bank Carolina I wrote
. You know I but you may be his pops but
how to save your dad's life. That's
bad. Well don't you see your father doesn't
go to the same truths inspired or does
that's awful do you think maybe you feel
father knew about it in time he would
rather die than to take blood from
a man of another religion we do want
to die with you mom one of the die no
not silent religion makes no
difference except maybe to
a Nazi or somebody is stupid by people
all over the world worship God in many
different ways God created everybody he
didn't create one people dead in the
neither your blood to same as mine mine's
the same as his. Do you know what this
wonderful country is
made up it's made up of
a hundred different kind of people and
a hundred different ways of talking and I
hundred different ways are going to to it
but they're all American way wouldn't we
be silly if we went around hating people
because they call in that had
different. Wouldn't we be
a lot of adults my dad came from
a valley but I'm an American but shit I
hate your father because he came from
Ireland or France or Russia would not be
a first class that had you guys remember
Pearl Harbor why the Japs stock that so it
looked like we could never
do anything about it but
a couple of days later something very
important happened close your eyes let me
tell you about it going Glenn Close your
eyes on if you want to imagine. There was
a job battleship the whole room and one
of our planes bought it you know what it
takes to bomb
a battleship it takes God no wow in
teamwork and boys who needed plenty of it
because that's what's thrown up and I like
to get out and walk home but the pilot
had only one thing on his mind to get
over that. And he did and the Bombardier
pushed the button on a five on
a bomber. Yep they sank
it. And every American threw his head back
and felt much better the pilot of that
ship was named Cole and
killing an American and
a Presbyterian you know dropped the
bombs my eleven an American and
a Jew you think maybe they should call the
bombing off because they had different
religion think about it that's
obvious. You know if you
a good American had to let anybody
make suckers out. I don't know what do
you say.
They are saying here and no hits and
a lot of. America through.
A. Lie going. A certain
word the democracy.
Was his own murder because.
I was so I live in. A plot
hole the earth's story
grows. What good enough
people old I thought I made.
But serials running
high ground based that.
Already done to religion.
That's the murder
come. As it is so I
work in. A work good idea
my thought was. A little
taller
a city where my people only. The how do
we know how unfair the
error of feeling for. The
raw Irish speak my mind off. The matter.
Being with. Things I've bought. The big.
In the small of the little calling her
a new strength and the house so
Miles told the wedding Aaron the
carrot jar the last Greg
McCrary. This rare memory
where no courage. Bar the murder. Or.
The. Green The.
Pavement God of the city. Or garden all in
room. The third's the
school owner club car the
mirror liar ties. But
especially during the
people all right. See. Saw.
Her and what. Do
we mean. In.
The one man Ragnar.
Alan. And.